Konkon
Episode 1: FIRST STROKE
Sukeban Magical Girl
Dark Academy
Director: Natsuko Hirose
Director Natsuko Hirose's
next work is here!
Opening Next Spring
Today Is Yesterday,
Tomorrow Is Now,
And Every Day Is Summer
HATSUKOI:
First Love
Director Natsuko Hirose's new animated film:
HATSUKOI: First Love
I can't wait for Director Natsuko Hirose's new movie
I've found something to live for again!
Konkon
HATSUKOI: First Love
Announcement PV
Redo these, please
HATSUKOI:
First Love
Announcement PV
Fix all
Opening Next Spring
Today Is Yesterday,
Tomorrow Is Now,
And Every Day Is Summer.
Director / Natsuko Hirose
HATSUKOI:
First Love
Clam Lunch
The only reason I'm still alive is to see Natsuko Hirose's next movie
Orenka
Natsuko Hirose
works are the best!!!
I'm a fan for life!!!!
Natsuko Hirose
Top
Latest
Images
Users
Videos
The only reason I'm still alive is to see Natsuko Hirose's next movie
I can't stand Natsuko Hirose. Seriously, I don't want
to even see her name.
Natsuko Hirose
works are the best!!!
I'm a fan for life!!!!
Devil Fish Ishizuka
Germanium
There's no point watching Natsuko Hirose stuff.
Total waste of time.
I can't stand Natsuko Hirose. Seriously, I don't want
to even see her name.
Natsuko Hirose
Top
Latest
Images
Users
Videos
Search
MP News
[Obituary]
Kametaro Tsuruyama (60) dies.
Kametaro Tsuruyama, renowned virtuoso of the
anime industry, known for many works including
the feature film, A Tale of Perishing, has died.
A wombat named Taro from the zoo heads to the moon.
He underwent rigorous training to make it come true.
The deceased animation director
(Photo from 2012)
The Void Is Coming!
Original Story & Director/Kametaro Tsuruyama
Planning/Studio Konkon
Saturday
Nights at
6:30 PM
on
Matsu TV
A Cat, a Cat!
You're Going to Become a Mountain Cat!
Saturday
Nights at
6:30 PM
on
Matsu TV
Serval Cat Mask
The Void Is Coming!
Original Story & Director/Kametaro Tsuruyama
Planning/Studio Konkon
Ikudas
Gifts
from
the
president
Konkon
Expires
Clam Lunch
Microwave
Instructions
Episode 2: "DEFEND"